Bhargav Borse

♥ Vadodara, IndiaMaterial by bhargavborse4898@gmail.comLanguage +91 8160606663Image: bhargavborse.app

■ About Me

Experience Designer and Frontend developer with experience in building webapps based on Pure HTML + CSS + JavaScript. Successfully completed multiple unique projects, each one having its own set of accomplished challenges. Love to experiment with modern technologies. Looking forward to starting my journey as a frontend developer at a company which will not only challenge me but help me develop my skillset further.

Education

Master of Computer Application

2019 - present

Parul University *⊘*

-7.76/10 CGPA in Semester 4

Bachelor of Computer Application

2016 - 2019

Navrachana University ∂

Enlighten Infosystems ∂

- Graduated with 6.68/10 CGPA

Professional Experience

May 2018 - Jun 2019

Software Intern

- Wrote code on JavaScript using Visual Studio and Firebase.
- Evaluated project requirements & specifications correctly and developed software application that surpassed mentor's expectations.
- Code available under FreedomForFashion ℰ repository.

🖰 Projects

REIG *❷* May 2018 - Oct 2018

Remainder and Event in Group

- Web Application based on JavaScript, Pure HTML + CSS + BOOTSTRAP and Progressive Web Apps.
- Online realtime chat, storing and sharing images, documents with the help of Firebase.
- In addition to this creating Event and Reminder for the user was also integrated.

F4F *⊘* Dec 2018 - May 2019

Freedom for Fashion

- Web Application based on JavaScript and HTML + CSS + BOOTSTRAP and Progressive Web App.
- Online rental portal for the customers who are in need of costumes.



Frontend Developer (JavaScript, HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap)

Backend Developer (C#, PHP, MySQL, NoSQL, Firebase)

Misc (GitHub, VS Code, Adobe XD, Adobe Illustrator, Adobe Photoshop)



👼 Certificates

Google Garage | Digital Marketing

Very Delighted to be Google certified in Digital Marketing. It was a well designed course covering a lot of topics: SEO, SEM, Content Marketing Strategy, Social Media, Search Campaign Analytics, Business Strategy, eCommerce, Web Traffic and PPC.

Cisco | Introduction to Cyber Security

Very Delighted to be Cisco certified in Cyber Security. It was a well designed and detailed course to get started on Cyber Security. It was all based on Global implications of cyber thefts, Vulnerable Attack, Cisco's approach to threat detection and defense